# **JAKE BAEK**

WEB DEVELOPER TORONTO, ON

# jakejonggubaek@gmail.com

- 519-330-8892
- /jakejonggubaek
- Portfolio: jakeisbaek.com

# PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a web developer with front and back end skills necessary to develop responsive web design as well as dry, clean and accessible applications. My passion for problem solving, an eagerness to learn and adapt to new technologies are strengthened by my previous experiences in web development & consulting roles.

# SKILLS

Front End Skills



HTML5







JavaScript





React







Responsive UII

SASS

WCAG

Back End Skills











node.js JAVA

SQL

NoSQL

XMI

Other Skills













SEO

Git

A/B test MS office

# CERTIFICATE

# Codecademy

Node.js

- Vue.js
- jQuery

# EDUCATION

# Juno College, JavaScript / Immersive Bootcamp AUG 2020 - MAR 2021

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript / ES6, React, REST APIs, Firebase, Git
- Responsive UI, accessibility(WCAG), Paired programming

#### Hanyang Univ., Urban Engineering FEB 2007 - FEB 2013

• GPA(4.01/4.5), Statistical Programming(SAS), Data Analysis, Adobe Photoshop, Mathematics, Physics, GIS

# RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

# Juno College, Mentor APR 2021 - PRESENT

Assist cohort 32, 33, Coding 101 Workshop

# Samsung SDS, Junior Web Developer JAN 2013 - JUL 2015

- Managed main page, sign in, log in/out systems (https://samsungfire.com/m) using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, SQL, SVN in a cross functional team.
- Improved client's (Samsung F&M Insurance) web application with TDD without any issue, and maintained the system by proactively monitoring live logs to ensure quality with responsibility.
- Carried out many projects by collaborating with different companies in fast-paced environments. Applied new security tools, enhanced accessibility, and launched a new mobile application.

## PROJECTS

# Popsipoll, <link>

HTML, CSS, SASS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, FIREBASE

 A responsive React project that provides create / share / vote polls & poll results with dark / light mode and preview poll functions.

# Random Recipe, <link>

HTML, CSS, SASS, JAVASCRIPT, RESTFUL API, PAIRED PROGRAMMING

 A responsive web application that provides random recipe based on what users have in their fridge.

## Team To-Do-List, <link>

HTML, SASS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, NODE, JS, MONGODB

• A full stack application that provides to-do-list and realtime chat which users can share with their teammates.